Mohamed Adnan

Sr.Graphic Designer

Address: Iraq, Baghdad, Wazeryia Phone: +9647838000622 Email: mo71med@outlook.com Date of birth: Sep 14, 2003

Nationality: Iraqi

Experience

Nov2022 - Present **Full-time**



Senior Graphic Designer
Ridha Alwan Coffee Baghdad

Sep 2022 - Present

Contract



Design Lead

HRES AGENCY Baghdad

Apr 2022 - Aug 2022

Contract



Graphic Designer

Fedshi Baghdad

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Full-time



Graphic Designer

Crazy Town Agency Baghdad

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

Full-time



Senior Graphic Designer

Palm Of Babylon- POB Baghdad

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

Full-time



Senior Graphic Designer

Elabelz Baghdad

Dec 2019 - May 2020

Full-time



MW Graphic Designer

HAMA Group Sulaymaniah

Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

Full-time



Graphic Designer

May 2018 - Dec 2018

Full-time



Morse Agency Baghdad

Graphic Designer

Majillano Baghdad

Education

Highschool diploma

Al-adhamyiah highschool Baghdad

About me

Hello!, My Name is Mohamed Adnan im 19 Years of age, i Started Working in the Advertising industry Since i Was 15 Years old, a bit early you could say, im fasinated by the idea of Design, the idea of Solving Problems by creating shapes or systems that interact with people, i find it very beautiful and interesting, and im looking for a new Challenge!

Languages

Arabic

Native

English

Advanced



